1.	Is autism something people are born with?
2.	How do I know if I have autism?
3.	How to treat people with autism?
4.	How to be good friends with someone with autism?
5.	What is autism spectrum disorder?
6.	What are the signs of autistic children?
7.	What causes autism?
8.	Can autism be treated?
9.	What do intervention methods for children with autism include?
10.	How can I help my child if he or she has autism?
11.	My child doesn't like looking into other people's eyes. Why so?
12.	How to communicate effectively with your child?
13.	My child often repeats certain actions over and over again. Why so?
14.	How to help your child calm down?
15.	How to help your child sleep better?
16.	How to help your child concentrate better?
17.	How to help your child learn better?
18.	Who should I talk to if I'm worried about my child?
19.	How to help your child express emotions?
20.	My child often self-stimulates. How to minimize this behavior?
21.	How to help your child control anger?
22.	How do children with autism grow up?
23.	How can I take care of myself if I have a child with ASD?
24.	How can I help my child improve their social skills?
25.	My child often has excessive reactions to loud noises or bright lights. How can I help them manage these situations?
26.	What should I do if my child struggles to understand non-verbal communication (e.g., body language)?
27.	My child has very specific and rigid interests. How can I support and encourage these interests in a positive way?
28.	I worry about my child's future after I can no longer care for them. How can I prepare for this future?
29.	How can I help my child integrate and participate in social activities, such as sports or clubs?
30.	I notice my child is prone to bullying. How can I protect them and help them handle this situation?
31.	How can I help my child adapt to new environments, such as changing schools or traveling?
32.	Can I identify and minimize the stimuli that my child frequently encounters?
33.	What should I do if my child often struggles with changes in schedule or environment?
34.	How can I help my child develop self-care skills, such as dressing themselves or cleaning up?
35.	I often find it challenging to go out with my child. How can I better prepare for and manage these activities?
36.	My child dislikes changing their eating habits. How can I diversify their diet in a healthy way?
37.	I feel exhausted and stressed when caring for my child. How can I maintain my mental health?
38.	I'm unsure if my child feels happy. How can I recognize and meet their happiness needs?
39.	How can I support my child when they encounter difficulties in movement and interacting with their environment?
40.	I want my child to have more independence as they grow up. How can I start preparing for this now?
